<xml>
  <apps>
    <title>Apps</title>
    <button>Learn More About New Apps</button>
    <header>Apps</header>
    <li_1_1h>IceWarp Desktop Documents</li_1_1h>
    <li_1_1>The most compatible office suite as known from WebClient that you can use offline. The apps can be installed on Windows, Mac or Linux. In Documents you get live font preview, two-column layout, printing support, spell-checker, equation editor, review mode and many other useful tools.</li_1_1>
    <li_1_2h>IceWarp Desktop Spreadsheets</li_1_2h>
    <li_1_2>Crunch numbers like a professional with powerful formulas, filters, diagrams, pivot tables and much more. You can search through large data files as well as use conditional formatting to highlight the values you need, then print it all out or export to PDF.</li_1_2>
    <li_1_3h>IceWarp Desktop Presentations</li_1_3h>
    <li_1_3>The application will be immediately familiar to all Microsoft PowerPoint users. It’s a lifesaver if you only need to fix an error in a presentation or wish to start creating from the grounds up using templates, styles and effects.</li_1_3>
    <li_1_4h>IceWarp Desktop Client</li_1_4h>
    <li_1_4>Email, calendar, contacts and instant messaging in one application for Windows that lets you work offline. You can have  multiple accounts and use it with your work email as well as Gmail, iCloud and Outlook.com at once. Find any email, attachment or contact in seconds thanks to the fast full-text search.</li_1_4>
    <li_1_5h>IceWarp TeamChat Desktop</li_1_5h>
    <li_1_5>Directly from Desktop Client you can open a dedicated application which lets you work with multiple TeamChat accounts at once, which is invaluable if you are active in several TeamChat organizations and  wouldn’t be easily possible in the web version.</li_1_5>
    <li_1_6h>IceWarp FileSync</li_1_6h>
    <li_1_6>Keep all your essential files up-to-date and available from everywhere with the online storage*. Easily share files with others as a link that you can send in a message. Just install FileSync on every Windows, Mac and Linux computer you have. It’s your virtual cloud-based drive.</li_1_6>
    <li_1_7h>IceChat</li_1_7h>
    <li_1_7>Chat on the go, instantly share photos or your location from your iPhone or Android. Install the app, log in and you´ll find your contact list already there with IceChat ready to use right away. For a sense of added privacy you can lock a conversation or the entire app with your fingerprint (iOS) or PIN (Android). The new version of IceChat on iOS now brings you the option of audio and video calls.</li_1_7>
    <note1>* Storage size is shared with your mailbox quota.</note1>
  </apps>
  <chat>
    <title>TeamChat</title>
    <header>Welcome to IceWarp TeamChat!</header>
    <first_paragraph>TeamChat is a collaboration tool for teams &amp; projects. It has the familiar interface of multi-user WebChat but extends it with file sharing, conference calls and much more. Here are a few tips to get you started with TeamChat.</first_paragraph>
    <li_1_1h>Quickly switch to TeamChat</li_1_1h>
    <li_1_1>A dot over its icon means there are unread messages in one of your chat rooms. Next to every chat room it shows number of unread messages since your last visit.</li_1_1>
    <li_1_2h>Public and private chat rooms</li_1_2h>
    <li_1_2>By now you are already a member of a public chat room that anyone can see and join, or you have been invited to a private chat room created by someone in your team.</li_1_2>
    <li_1_3h>Create a chat room</li_1_3h>
    <li_1_3>Chat rooms are organized into groups (such as by departments) preset by administrator. Click the + next to a group to create a room in it and then invite others.</li_1_3>
    <li_1_5h>Invite guests, share links or files</li_1_5h>
    <li_1_5>The plus icon to the left of where you type messages allows you to invite guests, send files, share links and few other options.  On the right you can insert emoticons.</li_1_5>
    <li_1_6h>Manage members and guests</li_1_6h>
    <li_1_6>Members are from your company, they can create new rooms and also remove or add more people to a chat room they have created. Guests are external users, such as consultants on your project, and you can freely add and remove them.</li_1_6>
    <li_1_7h>Manage files and documents</li_1_7h>
    <li_1_7>This tab contains list of files and documents that were uploaded by users of the chat room. Hover over the selected file and you can share it through the “Share” button.</li_1_7>
    <li_1_8h>Create or join events</li_1_8h>
    <li_1_8>This tab lists upcoming events created by room members for others. Select to accept or decline the conference invitation.</li_1_8>
    <li_1_9h>Open documents from chat bubbles</li_1_9h>
    <li_1_9>To open a document, click the document preview in the chat area. Similarly you can accept/decline a conference or join a conference call directly from the chat area.</li_1_9>
    <li_1_10h>Pin, like and comment on posts</li_1_10h>
    <li_1_10>TeamChat has the usual social features such as likes, dislikes, comments and emojis. Sort out unused chat rooms by moving them to Inactive rooms. Pin an interesting content for yourself or make it a public bookmark.</li_1_10>
    <li_1_11h>Collaboration on E-mails in TeamChat</li_1_11h>
    <li_1_11>Improve team collaboration and de-clutter your inbox by sharing your e-mails to TeamChat. With this new feature you can review, edit and send e-mails directly from your TeamChat room.</li_1_11>
  </chat>
</xml>
