<xml>
  <whatsnew>
    <title>Yeni Ne Var</title>
    <header>WebClient 11.3</header>
    <first_paragraph>This update of WebClient makes it the first web-based email to bring you WebDocuments – viewing Office documents right in your browser. We have partnered with LibreOffice to enable document editing and collaboration in the next release.</first_paragraph>
    <li_1_1h>WebDocuments</li_1_1h>
    <li_1_1>Click a file in Documents to preview Excel, PowerPoint, Word and all Open Document Format files directly in your browser without having to install any Office suite on your computer. Click inside the document preview to see any edits, search, zoom or open it in a separate window.</li_1_1>
    <li_1_2h>Meeting Invitations</li_1_2h>
    <li_1_2>In addition to Accept and Decline replies to meeting invitation, you can now provide a Tentative response, provide a reason when declining, and Propose a new time for the meeting right from the invitation email.</li_1_2>
    <li_1_3h>Auto-Hiding Folders</li_1_3h>
    <li_1_3>The folder tree on the left is automatically minimized to make room for content when the window is too small. Restore it by clicking the large icons on the left. Right-click the Home icon to change the panel appearance.</li_1_3>
    <li_1_4h>Auto-Hiding IM Contacts</li_1_4h>
    <li_1_4>The IM contact list on the right is minimized to make room for content, but you can still see your contacts’ photos and online statuses. Restore it to full size by hovering the mouse over it. Right-click inside the panel to change its appearance.</li_1_4>
    <li_1_5h>Multi-Line List</li_1_5h>
    <li_1_5>Contacts, Tasks, Notes, Files now offer the same multi-line List as emails when using Preview Pane. For example in contacts, you will see email addresses, phone numbers and photos right in the contact list.</li_1_5>
    <li_1_6h>Zoom to Events</li_1_6h>
    <li_1_6>When in month view, quickly zoom into the detailed agenda for a particular day by clicking the small calendar icon next to the date label. From there it’s possible to move events, create new appointments and so on.</li_1_6>
    <li_1_7h>Multiple Sent &amp; Trash Folders</li_1_7h>
    <li_1_7>When you add an external account in Options – Other Accounts, you can define its own Sent folder, as well as separate Trash folder to restore deleted items back to the account’s mailbox.</li_1_7>
    <li_1_8h>Delete Folders to Trash</li_1_8h>
    <li_1_8>When deleting one of the primary account’s folder, it is now moved to Trash including any subfolders. This feature prevents accidental deletion; the folder can be restored by a single click including its contents.</li_1_8>
    <li_1_9h>Auto Save Contacts, Calendars</li_1_9h>
    <li_1_9>Similar to email drafts, when adding new contacts, calendars, notes, the item is saved every few minutes without having to click OK. The Cancel button does nothing once an edited item is autosaved. Use Options – Calendar – Autosave GroupWare items to set this feature up.</li_1_9>
    <li_1_10h>Chat Notifications</li_1_10h>
    <li_1_10>To help you stay focused, incoming chat notifications no longer flash in the contact list or inside tabbed conversations. Instead they are highlighted by a blue bullet overlaying the contact&apos;s photo.</li_1_10>
  </whatsnew>
</xml>
