<xml>
	<whatsnew>
		<title>What&apos;s New</title>
		<header>WebClient 11.4</header>
		<first_paragraph>Build amazing things together – all you need is the built-in TeamChat collaboration tool. And with the other improvements we have added, your online productivity apps will feel completely natural.</first_paragraph>

		<li_1_1h>WebDocuments Editing*</li_1_1h>
		<li_1_1>Click a document once to preview it. Click into the preview and start making edits! This works with Excel sheets, PowerPoint presentations, Word documents and all ODF files. No Office on your computer needed.</li_1_1>

		<li_1_2h>Fullscreen Video</li_1_2h>
		<li_1_2>Fullscreen video mode is available for screensharing and video calls. To fill the entire screen, use the controls provided for video content in your browser (different in Internet Explorer, Firefox, Chrome).</li_1_2>

		<li_1_3h>Calendar Printing</li_1_3h>
		<li_1_3>You can now print your calendar including bar graphics, which means that you will print exactly what you see on the screen. The printing option is possible within Day, Week or Month views.</li_1_3>

		<li_1_4h>Compact View</li_1_4h>
		<li_1_4>See more items at once without having to scroll through long lists. By enabling the new compact view in Options - General you can see about 50% more messages, contacts, files compared to the spacious view.</li_1_4>

		<li_1_5h>New WebChat Notifications</li_1_5h>
		<li_1_5>When someone sends you a chat message, the contact slides to top of the contact list and gets a blue bullet over the photo. Easily get back to last closed chat windows by clicking the Recent Chats area.</li_1_5>

		<li_1_6h>Show Contact Card</li_1_6h>
		<li_1_6>Access the contact information right from the reading pane. Click on the email address and choose Show Contact Card to get the full contact details and additional options to work with the contact.</li_1_6>

		<li_1_7h>Expand a Distribution List</li_1_7h>
		<li_1_7>When addressing an email message to a distribution list you have created before, you can expand it to individual recipients in the To: field and then remove one or more names from it before sending.</li_1_7>

		<li_1_8h>Meeting Invitations</li_1_8h>
		<li_1_8>When you make changes to existing meetings, you can choose whether to notify other meeting attendees of the changes or don’t notify. Tentative events can now be accepted/declined directly from the calendar.</li_1_8>

		<li_1_9h>Working with All Attendees</li_1_9h>
		<li_1_9>You can invite all email recipients to a meeting. And vice-versa, when you double-click an existing meeting in your calendar, you can email all the attendees using a small envelope icon on the Attendees tab.</li_1_9>

		<li_1_10h>Auto-Hiding Panels</li_1_10h>
		<li_1_10>Folder panel on the left and WebChat panel on the right can be automatically hidden when not in use or when the screen area is too small. Change their behavior under the preview icon in the main toolbar.</li_1_10>

		<li_1_11h>TeamChat</li_1_11h>
		<li_1_11>Join the chat room and start to discuss ideas, share files or schedule events. Organize your conversations around a project, a topic a team, or anything you want. Invite anyone including external team mates.</li_1_11>

		<video>Watch a short video introduction to new WebDocuments</video>

		<note>* The feature needs to be enabled in your organization.</note>
	</whatsnew>
	<chat>
		<title>TeamChat</title>
		<header>Welcome to IceWarp TeamChat!</header>
		<first_paragraph>TeamChat is a collaboration tool for teams &amp; projects. It has the familiar interface of multi-user WebChat but extends it with file sharing, meetings, conference calls and much more. Here are a few tips to get you started with TeamChat.</first_paragraph>

		<li_1_1h>Quickly switch to TeamChat</li_1_1h>
		<li_1_1>A dot over its icon means there are unread messages in one of your chat rooms. Next to every chat room it shows number of unread messages since your last visit.</li_1_1>

		<li_1_2h>Public and private chat rooms</li_1_2h>
		<li_1_2>By now you are already a member of a public chat room that anyone can see and join, or you have been invited to a private chat room created by someone in your team.</li_1_2>

		<li_1_3h>Create a chat room</li_1_3h>
		<li_1_3>Chat rooms are organized into groups (such as by departments) preset by administrator. Click the + next to a group to create a room in it and then invite others.</li_1_3>

		<li_1_4h>Send private messages</li_1_4h>
		<li_1_4>Click a user’s photo and the message you type next will be sent only to that user. This way you can talk openly and in private without even leaving the chat room.</li_1_4>

		<li_1_5h>Invite guests, share links or files</li_1_5h>
		<li_1_5>The plus icon to the left of where you type messages allows you to invite guests, send files, share links and few other options.  On the right you can insert emoticons.</li_1_5>

		<li_1_6h>Manage members and guests</li_1_6h>
		<li_1_6>Members are from your company, they can create new rooms and also remove or add more people to a chat room they have created. Guests are external users, such as consultants on your project, and you can freely add and remove them.</li_1_6>

		<li_1_7h>Manage files and documents</li_1_7h>
		<li_1_7>This tab contains list of files and documents that were uploaded by users of the chat room. Hover over the selected file and you can share it through the “Share” button.</li_1_7>

		<li_1_8h>Create or join events</li_1_8h>
		<li_1_8>This tab lists upcoming events created by users of the room for the other members. Select to accept or decline the meeting invitation..</li_1_8>

		<li_1_9h>Open documents from chat bubbles</li_1_9h>
		<li_1_9>To open a document, click its preview image in the chat area. You can also accept/decline a meeting, or join a conference call directly from its bubble in the chat area.</li_1_9>
	</chat>
</xml>