<xml>
  <apps>
    <title>应用程序</title>
    <button>了解更多关于新版本应用程序的内容</button>
    <header>应用程序</header>
    <li_1_1h>IceWarp 桌面文档</li_1_1h>
    <li_1_1>用户可以离线使用与WebClient兼容的办公套件，该办公套件中的应用程序可安装在安装在Wiindows,Mac或者Linux上，例如通过Documents应用程序您可以获得实时字体预览、分列布局、打印、拼写检查、方程式编辑器、审阅模式等其他等多的文档工具。</li_1_1>
    <li_1_2h>IceWarp 桌面表格</li_1_2h>
    <li_1_2>通过强大的公式、过滤器、图表、透视表等功能处理数字，使处理变得更专业化，用户可以搜索大数据文件，也可以使用条件格式直接找到您需要的数据，然后将其全部打印出来或导到PDF文件。</li_1_2>
    <li_1_3h>IceWarp 桌面演示文稿</li_1_3h>
    <li_1_3>该应用程序很快会被微软PowerPoint用户所熟知，如果用户只需要修复演示文稿中的错误，或者只是需要使用模板、样式和效果从头开始创建，那么该应用程序能给您省去不少的麻烦。</li_1_3>
    <li_1_4h>IceWarp 桌面客户端</li_1_4h>
    <li_1_4>安装在Windows系统的一个应用程序中的电子邮件、日历、联系人和即时消息可供用户离线使用。您可以将多个账户与工作邮件一起使用，比如一次使用 Gmail, iCloud 和 Outlook.com等账户，借助快速全文搜索，您可以在几秒钟内找到任何电子邮件、附件或联系人。</li_1_4>
    <li_1_5h>IceWarp TeamChat 桌面应用</li_1_5h>
    <li_1_5>Directly from Desktop Client you can open a dedicated application which lets you work with multiple TeamChat accounts at once, which is invaluable if you are active in several TeamChat organizations and  wouldn’t be easily possible in the web version.&#13;&#10;您可以直接通过桌面客户端直接打开你需要的专属客户端，这样您可以同时使用多个TeamChat 账户参与团队协作，节省了宝贵的工作时间，极大的提高了工作效率。一人同时活跃多个TeamChat组织，在web版本的实现是具有一定难度的，但如今通过我们的专属客户端可以轻易做到。</li_1_5>
    <li_1_6h>IceWarp 文件同步</li_1_6h>
    <li_1_6>只需在您所拥有的Windows, Mac 和 Linux系统上安装FileSync，就可享受基于虚拟云的在线存储文件的功能，在线存储*可以保持不错过任何地方的存储文件，并且文件一直处于更新的最新状态，甚至可以作为您发送消息中的一条链接轻松的与其他人分享文件。</li_1_6>
    <li_1_7h>IceChat</li_1_7h>
    <li_1_7>在您的手机上安装IceChat应用程序，并完成注册和登录就可以使用，手机版Chat智能的与您的电脑版Chat的联系人进行同步，手机登录后页面就直接显示您的Chat联系人，不仅可以享受沟通的乐趣还可以通过手机即时分享照片和位置，并且iOS上的新版IceChat现在为用户提供了音频和视频通话选项功能。为了增强用户的隐私安全，用户可以用指纹(iOS)或PIN (Android)锁定对话或整个应用程序。</li_1_7>
    <note1>* 存储大小与您的邮箱容量共享.</note1>
  </apps>
  <chat>
    <title>TeamChat</title>
    <header>欢迎来到 IceWarp TeamChat!</header>
    <first_paragraph>TeamChat is a collaboration tool for teams &amp; projects. It has the familiar interface of multi-user WebChat but extends it with file sharing, conference calls and much more. Here are a few tips to get you started with TeamChat.</first_paragraph>
    <li_1_1h>快速切换到 TeamChat</li_1_1h>
    <li_1_1>A dot over its icon means there are unread messages in one of your chat rooms. Next to every chat room it shows number of unread messages since your last visit.</li_1_1>
    <li_1_2h>公共聊天室和私人聊天室</li_1_2h>
    <li_1_2>By now you are already a member of a public chat room that anyone can see and join, or you have been invited to a private chat room created by someone in your team.</li_1_2>
    <li_1_3h>创建一个聊天室</li_1_3h>
    <li_1_3>Chat rooms are organized into groups (such as by departments) preset by administrator. Click the + next to a group to create a room in it and then invite others.</li_1_3>
    <li_1_5h>邀请, 共享链接和文件</li_1_5h>
    <li_1_5>The plus icon to the left of where you type messages allows you to invite guests, send files, share links and few other options.  On the right you can insert emoticons.</li_1_5>
    <li_1_6h>管理人员和访客</li_1_6h>
    <li_1_6>Members are from your company, they can create new rooms and also remove or add more people to a chat room they have created. Guests are external users, such as consultants on your project, and you can freely add and remove them.</li_1_6>
    <li_1_7h>管理文件和文档</li_1_7h>
    <li_1_7>This tab contains list of files and documents that were uploaded by users of the chat room. Hover over the selected file and you can share it through the “Share” button.</li_1_7>
    <li_1_8h>创建时间或加入事件</li_1_8h>
    <li_1_8>This tab lists upcoming events created by room members for others. Select to accept or decline the conference invitation.</li_1_8>
    <li_1_9h>从聊天气泡打开文档</li_1_9h>
    <li_1_9>To open a document, click the document preview in the chat area. Similarly you can accept/decline a conference or join a conference call directly from the chat area.</li_1_9>
    <li_1_10h>Pin, like and comment on posts</li_1_10h>
    <li_1_10>TeamChat has the usual social features such as likes, dislikes, comments and emojis. Sort out unused chat rooms by moving them to Inactive rooms. Pin an interesting content for yourself or make it a public bookmark.</li_1_10>
    <li_1_11h>TeamChat中的电子邮件协作</li_1_11h>
    <li_1_11>Improve team collaboration and de-clutter your inbox by sharing your e-mails to TeamChat. With this new feature you can review, edit and send e-mails directly from your TeamChat room.</li_1_11>
  </chat>
</xml>
